Starting benchmark on repository: C:\Users\Witbix\Wamious

[Load & Retrieval] Walked 170 files in 233ms
[Load & Retrieval] Parsed AST for source files in 607ms
[Load & Retrieval] Extracted 0 git commits in 127ms

=> Total Load & Retrieval Time: 968ms

[Token Usage Estimates - Baseline before RAG]
Architecture Agent Prompt Payload: ~4813 tokens
Onboarding Agent Prompt Payload: ~4813 tokens
Tech Debt Agent Prompt Payload: ~4813 tokens
Security Agent Prompt Payload: ~3099 tokens
History Agent Prompt Payload: ~1 tokens

=> Estimated Total Tokens Per Repo Scan: ~17539 tokens

Metrics generation complete. These baseline metrics show the heavy token overhead of passing raw JSON arrays to LLMs, justifying the move to a RAG / Vector DB architecture.
